Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 6\h\h\hRuche the Pierrot
Panic
Whisper
Tee-hee
Skill Tree: [Lady Luck]
In Magic World,
Dungeons (Dreamholes)
are the nightmares of the
sleeping God of Creation, Alxeros.
Angel's Playbox Entrance
Recommended Level: 50
Ruche Luvis
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Attack
Defense
Magic
Speed
Equipment
Ironpiercer
Special Skills
Cat's Paw
Titles
Rank F Adventurer
Common Skills
Dice Thrust
Dice Thrust [Common Skill]
A thrusting skill
Rolls a six-sided die and grants an
additional effect based on the rolled result
Skill Tree: Pierrot
Remaining Skill Points:
The Fool's Acrobatics
Lady Luck
Attack Booster
Ironpiercer
Ironpiercer Recommended Level: 18
Attack: +3
Market Price: 550,000G
This knife is effective against tough opponents
When damage is applied, reduce the target's
defense by 15% before calculating damage
Monster: Patchwork Bear
Shadow Stomp
Step on a target's shadow to prevent
them from fleeing. The effect ends as
soon as your foot is no longer touching
the ground
Bear Shield [Recommended Level: 10]
Defense: +12
Market Price: 200,000G
A cute round bear shield
Low recommended level for its stats
Special Skill
Cat's Paw
Luck